

Adenuga Abiola Jude

IT/ICT Coordinator

Mobile: +249905970319

otunbajude@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/adenuga-jude/

Profile

I am a third culture adult that went to university in the UK for my first degree, and have enjoyed living abroad for over a decade. I have found that my passion lies in returning the gifts that I was given: a learning environment that both engages and challenges young minds while fostering intercultural awareness and global mindedness. I am a "tech-guy" that recognizes that the most important technology tool could still be a marker and whiteboard, depending on the situation and individuals' needs. I am an advocate of purposeful use of technology who always emphasizes the "why" before the "how".

CERTIFICATIONS

- Department of Education (UK) Qualified Teacher Status (QTS)
- Hawaii State Licensed K-12 Computer Science, EAL and Design Technology Teacher
- International Society of Technology in Education (ISTE) certified
- International Baccalaureate Middle Years Programme (MYP) Design Technology (Category 2)
- International Baccalaureate Diploma Programme (DP) Computer Science (Category 1)
- Computer Science Teacher Association active membership
- Google Certified User Experience Designer
- University of London ICT in Primary Education: Transforming Children's Learning Across the Curriculum
- University of London Supporting Children with Difficulties in Reading and Writing
- University of California Teaching Java Sequences, Primitive Types and Using Objects

EXPERIENCE

Khartoum International Community School, Sudan - ICT and Learning Support Teacher August 2020 - PRESENT

- **Provided** advisory support and pastoral care to homeroom students
- Led digital citizenship workshops using the Common Sense Education curriculum
- Coached U-14 male soccer team
- Provided learning support to EAL and SEN students using pull out and push in models
- **Developed** IEPs and **led** IEP team meetings
- Created instructional materials and trained teachers on the use of Moodle LMS
- **Taught** International Middle Years Curriculum (IMYC) ICT course using the Computer Science Teacher Association standards as the framework
- Advocated for and presented the MAP assessment to the Senior Leadership Team (SLT)

Beijing World Youth Academy, China - Design Teacher and Technology Integration Specialist August 2017 - June 2020

- **Facilitated** professional development and **mentored** teachers with regards to innovative teaching and learning (e.g. gaming/gamification of the classroom, flipped classroom, design thinking in curriculum development, etc)
- Offered pastoral and advisory support as a homeroom teacher
- Supervised and guided students as they work on their Service as Action (SA) projects
- Coached the U-14 male soccer team
- Collaborated with homeroom teachers to implement a digital citizenship program that aligns with the Common Core Education and International Society of Technology in Education (ISTE) curriculum and standards
- Taught Middle Years Program (MPY) Product and Digital Design courses using the Next Generation Science Standards for Engineering as the framework
- Launched Digital Citizenship Philosophy and Family Technology Agreement to support SEL related to technology use
- **Fostered** the development of computational thinking and programming via an after-school Lego robotics club

Hanoi Public Schools, Vietnam - ESL Teacher

August 2014 - June 2017

- **Taught** English as a second language to Hanoi public school students via a government contracted education agency
- Planned lessons and field trips that allowed students to engage in language exchange
- Facilitated Cambridge Preliminary English Test (PET) assessments and IELTS preparatory courses

United Nations International School (Hanoi), Vietnam - Substitute Teacher and Intern August 2014 - June 2017

- Completed clinical teaching at the ESL and Design departments
- Substitute taught various subjects and grade levels throughout the secondary school
- Chaperoned several service learning trips as part of the Week Without Walls program

American Education Group (Hanoi), Vietnam - Technology support and Algorithm teacher January 2012- June 2014

- **Installed** and maintained operating systems and hardwares
- **Upgraded** international bandwidth for on-site access by 60% at only a 30% increase in cost
- Slashed number of redundant IT systems from 7 4
- Taught block and text based programming language to middle and high school students

FPT Software (Hanoi), Vietnam - Intern

August 2011 - Dec 2011

- Worked as a user-experience designer and quality assurance tester
- Participated in the Siemens Empowered 2011 design sprint

EDUCATION

2019: University of Roehampton, London - Master of Arts in Technology and Learning Design

2017: Moreland University, Washington DC - Master of Education

2011: University of Greenwich, London - Bachelor of Science in Computing

References

- Lindsey Devillier Academic Deputy Principal, Beijing World Youth Academy
- Emmanuel Niyibizi Head of Secondary, Khartoum International Community School
- Alaa Alkmaly Director of Technology, Khartoum International Community School
- Charity Facchin Student Support Coordinator, Khartoum International Community School